healthfulpursuit.com 2019-06-11

# Healthful Pursuit Privacy Policy | Healthful Pursuit

**Healthful Pursuit Inc.** (“Company” or “we”, “our” or “us”) values our customers, including you (“you”) and we respect your privacy and personal information which is information about an identifiable individual (as defined by applicable privacy or data protection laws). This privacy policy (the “Policy”) describes the kinds of personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, how we protect it, and under what circumstances we share it with third parties. This Policy also describes the decisions you can make about your personal information. You may require us to change, amend or delete the personal information that you have provided to us at any time.

If this Policy changes in the future, we will post an updated version on our website at healthfulpursuit.com (the “Website”). We recommend that you check this Website periodically in order to review our current Policy. You can tell if this Policy has changed by checking the effective date that appears at the bottom of this Policy. Depending on the circumstances, we may also decide to send you a notice electronically that the Policy was changed. If you continue to visit healthfulpursuit.com after the Policy changed or notice of the change has been given, you will be deemed to have accepted such changes.

## Information We Collect

When you sign up to the Healthful Pursuit Newsletter, create a account or contact us, you voluntarily give us certain personal information including your e-mail address, first name, last name, state or province, and country. In addition, when you visit our Website, we collect certain information about your activity on our Website, as described below under the heading “Our use of Cookies and Log Files”. When you make a purchase through our Website, we do not collect your payment details. The data needed to process the payment is collected by the payment processor. We call this personal information “Sales Information”.

## Using Information We Collect

We use the personal information we collect about you in order to: communicate with you for the purposes you have separately indicated when you signed up to the Website; learn more about you and your product preferences by looking at, among other things, the IP address of your computer and your activity on the Website; and address problems with, and improve, our website design and services. If you would like to stop receiving promotional emails from Healthful Pursuit, you can opt-out by clicking on the Unsubscribe link found on the bottom of each promotional email.

In accordance with this Policy, we may share your personal information within Healthful Pursuit Inc. or with our service providers. We may also share information with our financial, insurance, legal, accounting or other advisors that provide professional services to us. We may also share information in a manner consistent with this Policy with third parties involved in providing educational resources, product recommendations, recipes, physical and digital products, as well as video and audio content. to you including payment processors, subcontractors or entities participating in our supply chains. We will not share, sell or rent your personal information in personally identifiable form with any third party, except if, and to the extent necessary, in our good faith judgment, doing so is required to: complete your purchase; comply with laws or regulations; respond to a valid subpoena, order, or government request; establish or exercise the Company’s legal rights or defend against legal claims; investigate, detect, supress, prevent or take action regarding illegal or prohibited activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the reputation or physical safety of any person; or as otherwise required by law.

We may remove personal identifiers from your information and maintain and use it in anonymous form that may later be combined with other information to generate aggregated information. Such anonymous and aggregated information may be sold, traded, rented, or shared.

We use the Sales Information in order to process and fulfill your order, send you e-mails to confirm your order status and shipment, send you products you order; and allow you to pay for products you order. If our Company is to be sold, merged or amalgamated or substantially all of its assets are to be sold or disposed of, your personal information may be transferred to a potential purchaser if, and to the extent necessary, it is required for the purposes of deciding whether to proceed with the proposed transaction and completing it. If such a sale, merger, acquisition or disposal is completed, the purchaser may use and disclose your personal information only to the extent described in this Policy if the information relates solely to the carrying on of the business or activity or the carrying out of the objects for which the sale, merger or acquisition took place.

We will retain your personal information only for a time and to the extent necessary for the purposes for which it was collected as described in this Policy and for reasonable backup, archival, audit, or other similar purposes.

## Your Decisions About Your Personal Information

At any time you can contact us to: stop receiving e-mails from us; review the personal information held by the Company in connection with your account; withdraw your consent for our use and disclosure of your information; request a list of third parties to which the Company may have provided your personal information; close your account; and amend your personal information, where possible, by clicking [https://healthfulpursuit.us4.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=d8e8a2f973c12814bc9c2c57c&id=590b00b5b3](https://healthfulpursuit.us4.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=d8e8a2f973c12814bc9c2c57c&id=590b00b5b3) or by emailing us at info@healthfulpursuit.com. You can always unsubscribe from receiving promotional e-mails from us by simply clicking the “unsubscribe” link provided at the bottom of every promotional e-mail from us.

If you contact us to do any of the things listed above, we may require you to provide sufficient personal information to allow us to identify you and tell you about the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and this personal information will only be used for this purpose. If you contact us about your personal information, we will respond to your request within a reasonable time and at no cost to you.

Generally, you may withdraw at any time your consent for us to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Policy, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. As such, we may continue to use your personal information as may be required to provide you with requested services, and to the extent that we are contractually obligated to do so or as necessary to enforce any contractual obligations you may have with us. If you refuse to provide us with the information we require or later contact us to withdraw your consent to use and disclose this information, we may no longer be able to provide you with free resources, audio and video content, digital and physical products, product recommendations, recipes, or any other information shared on healthfulpursuit.com.

## Our Use of Cookies and Log Files

We use browser tracking cookies (or “cookies”), which are small text files that are placed on the hard disk of a computer by a website. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a website or web server that issued the cookie to you. We also use browser “log files” which record certain information when you visit a website, including your internet protocol (IP) address. To improve your experience on our Website, we use cookies and logs files to: recognize you when you return to our website; keep track of activity on our Website and remember what items you have clicked on or viewed; study how you navigate through our website and which products you request in site searches so that we can improve the design, content and function of our Website; and customize the message, content and delivery of online banner advertisements and e-mails that reflect how you navigate to and through our Website based on your online behavior. We call this “Browsing Data”. We may hire third-party service providers to assist us in the collection and analysis of this Browsing Data collected through cookies, but none of your personal information is disclosed to these third party service providers.

You have the ability to accept or decline our use of cookies. You can refuse cookies by turning them off or blocking them in your internet browser. If you decide to turn off or block cookies, our website might not function correctly.

## Security

We aim to provide you with a safe experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, technological, and organizational safeguards to appropriately protect the security and privacy of your personal information against loss, theft, and unauthorized access, disclosure, copying use or modification. Please note, however, that while we try to create a secure and reliable Website for users, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from the Website or via e-mail cannot be guaranteed.

We limit access to your personal information within the Company to individuals on a need-to-know basis. Your personal information may be collected, used, processed, transferred, and retained in multiple countries including Canada, the United States, and the European Economic Area which may be outside the region in which you are situated and may have different privacy or data protection legislation, and may therefore be subject to the laws of these countries. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area or a country which restricts data transfers outside of that jurisdiction or region without your consent, you consent to your personal information being transferred outside of the European Economic Area or your country for processing or storage by or on behalf of the Company.

## Links to Other Sites

We provide links on our Website to other, third party sites we think you will enjoy. These sites operate independently of us and have established their own privacy and security policies. Any personal information you provide on linked pages or other sites is provided directly to that third party and subject to that third party’s privacy policy. We strongly encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit. This Policy does not apply to such linked pages or other sites, and we are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites which are provided solely for your convenience.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection

The Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 18. Company does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from any children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonably efforts to delete such personal information from our database.

## Questions or Comments

If you have any questions or comments or wish to make a complaint about this Policy, please feel free to contact via email at info@healthfulpursuit.com. If you contact us about your personal information, we will respond to your request within a reasonable time and at no cost to you.

Effective Date: December 7, 2017
